

ABOUT ME

I am a highly motivated and dedicated professional with a passion for technology and a desire to make a career switch from dentistry to software development. With 2 years of experience as a dentist, I have honed my communication and problemsolving skills and am now eager to apply these skills to a career in web development

TECHNICAL STACK

Express	••••
React	••••
Node	••••
MongoDB	••••
HTML/ CSS/ JS	••••
BootStrap 4	••••
Git/ Github	••••
Stripe	••••
Cloudinary	••••
Jira	••••
Postman	••••
Handlebars	••••
Canvas	••••

LANGUAGES

English

Malayalam

RESHMA NIDHISH

Full Stack Developer

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/reshmanidhish

https://github.com/reshmanidhish

OBJECTIVE

To work in a healthy, innovative and challenging environment extracting the best out of me, enhance my technical skills, make the learning curve as steep as possible and thereby be an asset to the organization.

PROJECTS

Stylio - An Ecommerce Home Decor

2023

Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars, MongoDB, Cloudinary, Stripe, Bootstrap

Stylio is an ecommerce platform for home decor. This project allows users to browse and purchase a wide range of home decor items, providing them with a seamless shopping experience

https://github.com/reshmanidhish/stylio

Supergirl's Heroic Quest Game

2023

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Canvas

Supergirl's Heroic Quest is an exciting and action-packed city-themed game which is developed with Canvas and DOM manipulation

https://github.com/reshmanidhish/supergirl-game

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp 03/2023 - 09/2023

Ironhack Berlin

Bachelor of Dental Surgery 2011 - 2015

Rajah Muthiah Dental College Annamalai University Tamil Nadu, India

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dentist 01/2017 - 07/2017

Kailas Dental Clinic

Kerala, India

- Dentist with a focus on compassionate patient care and comprehensive treatment
- Proficient in diagnostics, treatment planning, and various dental procedures
- Dedicated to patient education and fostering positive relationships

Dentist 07/2016 - 12/2016

NS Hospital

Kerala, India

- Delivered skilled dental care, diagnosing and treating oral health conditions
- Collaborated with diverse healthcare teams to ensure holistic patient well-being
- Promoted oral hygiene education, prioritizing preventive care for improved patient outcomes.

Dentist (Intern)

08/2015 - 06/2016

District Hospital

Kerala, India

- Assisted senior dentists in diverse patient care and treatments
- Conducted dental procedures, aiding treatment planning
- Contributed to patient education on oral hygiene practices